I'm really happy to see white people talking about the Rothschilds because like literally
when Nick Cannon asked a question about the Rothschilds on his podcast in like, I think
it was like 2019, they literally took away his shows.
He was like fired, I believe from Viacom.
He basically had to kiss the ring and he was represented by two Jewish folks and they
clearly are Zionists, but his manager and his agent who used to be my agent.
Yeah.
So I'm glad to see that white folks are also understanding that it's not just you that
need to be in the front lines, like with ICE, you need to be in the front lines of exposing
information that has literally ruined people's lives when they have attempted to expose it.
And it's not to say that white people haven't had their lives ruined too, but just saying
this is a guava pastry.